A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33; 276.7 Cubic Feet 725 document boxes
  - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1981 (Bulk: 1977-1981); 1977-1981; 25; 75.57 Cubic Feet 198 containers
    - Winthrop Rockefeller (and family), 9
      - Winrock Farms, Inc. (Box 611, Folder 3-4)
      - Rockefeller, Jeannette E. (Box 611, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul (Box 611, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Winrock International (Box 612, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul - Winrock Farms (Box 612, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Deborah Sage (Box 612, Folder 3)
      - Bartley, Bruce (Box 451, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1977-1981; 26; 8.92 Cubic Feet 21 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A (Box 613, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - B-C (Box 614, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - D-I (Box 615, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - J-N (Box 616, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - N-W (Box 617, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - W-Z (Box 618, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 618, Folder 3-4)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 618, Folder 5)
    - Contributions (Box 619, Folder 1)
    - Creel Committee (Box 619, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Philanthropy (Box 619, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Agency Task Force (Box 619, Folder 4, Box 620, Folder 1-2)
    - Finances (Box 620, Folder 3, Box 621, Folder 1-3, Box 622, Folder 1)
    - Grants (Box 622, Folder 2)
    - Grants - A-Z (Box 622, Folder 3)
    - International Program (Box 622, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Center for Political Alternatives (Box 622, Folder 5)
    - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation (Box 623, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) (Box 623, Folder 2-4)
    - Annual Meetings (Box 624, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1981 (Box 624, Folder 3, Box 625, Folder 1-3)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1980 (Box 626, Folder 1-5, Box 627, Folder 1)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1979 (Box 627, Folder 2-3, Box 628, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1978 (Box 628, Folder 3-5, Box 629, Folder 1-3, Box 630)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1977 (Box 631, Folder 1-5, Box 632, Folder 1-2)
    - National Program (Box 632, Folder 3)
    - National Resources Defense Council (Box 633, Folder 1)
    - New York City Program (Box 633, Folder 2)
    - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine (NYCOM) (Box 633, Folder 3-4, Box 634, Folder 1-2)
    - New York Zoological Society - Animal Kingdom Fund (Box 634, Folder 3)
    - Planning and Review Committee (Box 634, Folder 4, Box 635, Folder 1)
    - Phoenix House and Foundation, Inc. (Box 635, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Family (Box 635, Folder 3)
    - Solar Energy (Box 635, Folder 4)
    - Special Reports (Box 635, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1977-1981; 27; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller Family Fund - A-Z (Box 637, Folder 1-4)
    - Annual Reports (Box 638, Folder 1-3)
    - Annual Report 1980 (Box 638, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report 1979 (Box 638, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report 1978 (Box 638, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report 1977 (Box 638, Folder 7, Box 639, Folder 1-2)
    - Contributions (Box 636, Folder 5)
    - Finances (Box 636, Folder 6)
    - Grants (Box 639, Folder 3)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1978-1979 (Box 639, Folder 4)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1977 (Box 639, Folder 5, Box 640, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller Family Office, 1977-1981; 28; 4.56 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - General (Box 636, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - Board of Directors (Box 636, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - Board of Managers (Box 636, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Family Office - A-Z (Box 636, Folder 7)
    - 5600 Inc. (Box 636, Folder 8)
    - Matching Gifts (Box 636, Folder 9)
    - Office Operations (Box 641, Folder 1)
    - Personal Assistance Cases (Box 641, Folder 2)
    - Management (Box 641, Folder 3)
    - Office Directories (Box 641, Folder 4)
    - Task Force (Box 641, Folder 5)
    - Public Affairs - A-R (Box 640, Folder 3-4)
    - Public Affairs - S-Z (Box 642, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Peter Beter (Box 642, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs - Charles A. Lindbergh (Box 642, Folder 3-4, Box 643, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Alvin Moscow Material (Box 643, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs - Alvin Moscow Manuscript - Part I (Box 643, Folder 3-4)
    - Public Affairs - Alvin Moscow Manuscript - Part II (Box 644, Folder 1-2)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - A, C (Box 644, Folder 4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - C-G (Box 645, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - H-L (Box 646, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - M-R (Box 647, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - S-W (Box 648, Folder 1-5)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - W-Z (Box 649, Folder 1-2)
    - Public Affairs - JDR Jr. Credo (Box 649, Folder 3)
    - Public Affairs - Rockefeller Family News Summary, 1977-1980 (Box 649, Folder 4-7)
    - Public Affairs - Rockefeller Family News Summary, 1981 (Box 650, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977-1981; 29; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller Foundation - A-J (Box 650, Folder 2-4)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - K-Z (Box 651, Folder 1-4)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1977 (Box 652, Folder 1-2)
    - Printed Matter (Box 652, Folder 3)
    - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Youth Award (Box 652, Folder 4)
    - Villa Bellagio Conference Study Center (Box 653, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University, 1977-1981; 30; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller University - A-Z (Box 653, Folder 2-3)
    - Articles (Box 654, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 654, Folder 2)
    - Contributions (Box 654, Folder 3)
    - Council (Box 654, Folder 4)
    - Council - A-Z (Box 654, Folder 5)
    - Council - Meetings-Minutes (Box 654, Folder 6)
    - Council - David Rockefeller (Box 666, Folder 3)
    - Development Committee (Box 654, Folder 7)
    - Finances (Box 655, Folder 1)
    - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 655, Folder 2-4)
    - Fund Raising - RBF (Box 656, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller University - Minutes-Meetings (Box 656, Folder 3)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 656, Folder 4)
    - Fairfield Osborn Memorial (Box 656, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material (Box 656, Folder 6)
    - Releases (Box 657, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 657, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Contributions (Box 657, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Hillcrest Conference, 1981 October 9-10 (Box 657, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Leonard Outhwaite (Box 657, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - David Rockefeller material (Box 657, Folder 7, Box 658, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Printed Matter (Box 658, Folder 2)
    - Sutton House Associates (City Block) (Box 658, Folder 3)
    - Works of Art (Box 658, Folder 4)
  - S, 1977-1981; 31; 3.04 Cubic Feet 8 letter document boxes
    - S - Miscellaneous - S-SD (Box 658, Folder 5)
    - S - Miscellaneous - SE-SZ (Box 659, Folder 1-2)
    - Science - A-M (Box 659, Folder 3)
    - Science - N-Z (Box 660, Folder 1)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest (Box 660, Folder 2)
    - Science - Federation of American Scientist Fund (Box 660, Folder 3)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute (Box 660, Folder 4)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute - Printed Matter (Box 661, Folder 1)
    - Science - Institute of Society, Ethics and The Life Sciences (Box 661, Folder 2)
    - Science - Union of Concerned Scientists (Box 661, Folder 3)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-Z (Box 662, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - A-Z (Box 662, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Board of Trustees (Box 662, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Contributions (Box 662, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Finances (Box 662, Folder 5, Box 663, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Croton Associates (Box 663, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Minutes-Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 663, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Minutes-Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 664, Folder 1-5)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Printed Material and Clippings (Box 665, Folder 1)
  - T-W, 1977-1981; 32; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - T - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 2-3)
    - U - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 4)
    - V - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 5)
    - W - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 6, Box 666, Folder 1)
    - Westchester Organizations - A-Z (Box 666, Folder 2)
  - Welfare, 1977-1981; 33; 5.41 Cubic Feet 13 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Welfare - A-N (Box 667, Folder 1-3)
    - Welfare - O-Z (Box 668, Folder 1)
    - American Red Cross (Box 668, Folder 2-3)
    - Center for Community Change (Box 668, Folder 4)
    - Community Service Society (Box 669, Folder 1)
    - United Funds - A-Z (Box 669, Folder 2)
    - United Funds - United Way of Tri-State (Box 669, Folder 3)
    - USO (Box 669, Folder 4)
    - USO - Metropolitan New York (Box 670, Folder 1)
    - Tune-In (Box 670, Folder 2)
    - Visiting Nurse of New York (Box 670, Folder 3)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. (Box 670, Folder 4, Box 671, Folder 1)
    - Animals - A-Z (Box 671, Folder 2)
    - Animals - American Society for Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 671, Folder 3)
    - Animals - Animal Welfare Institute (Box 672, Folder 1)
    - Animals - Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 672, Folder 2)
    - Blind - A-Z (Box 672, Folder 3)
    - Community Centers - A-D (Box 672, Folder 4)
    - Community Centers - E-Z (Box 673, Folder 1)
    - Community Centers - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association (Box 673, Folder 2)
    - Community Centers - Fifth Avenue Community Center of Harlem Inc. (Box 673, Folder 3)
    - Crime Prevention - A-Z (Box 673, Folder 4)
    - Crime Prevention - Eisenhower Foundation for Prevention of Violence (Box 674, Folder 1)
    - Day Nurseries - A-Z (Box 674, Folder 2)
    - Family Counseling - A-Z (Box 674, Folder 3)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service Association of America (Box 674, Folder 4)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service of Nassau County (Box 674, Folder 5)
    - Handicapped - A-Z (Box 675, Folder 1-3)
    - Handicapped - International Center for the Disabled (Box 676, Folder 1)
    - Handicapped - ICD Rehabilitation and Research Center (Box 676, Folder 2)
    - Handicapped - ICD - Dinner re David Rockefeller, 1981 October 14 (Box 676, Folder 3)
    - Handicapped - Homes - A-Z (Box 676, Folder 4)
    - (Native American) Indians - A-N (Box 677, Folder 1-3)
    - (Native American) Indians - N-Z (Box 678, Folder 1)
    - (Native American) Indians - American Indian Institute (Box 678, Folder 2)
    - (Native American) Indians - Institute for Career and Vocational Training (Box 678, Folder 3)
    - (Native American) Indians - Institute for the Development of Indian Law, Inc. (Box 678, Folder 4)
    - (Native American) Indians - Native American Rights Fund (Box 678, Folder 5)
    - Legal - A-Z (Box 679, Folder 1-2)
    - Legal - Legal Aid Society (Box 679, Folder 3)
    - Legal - Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons (Box 679, Folder 4)
    - Musicians (Box 679, Folder 5)
    - Orphans (Box 680, Folder 1)
  - Women (Role of), 1977-1981; 34; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Women (Role of) - A-N (Box 680, Folder 2-4)
    - Women (Role of) - O-W (Box 681, Folder 1-3)
    - Catalyst (Box 681, Folder 4)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1978-1981 (Box 681, Folder 5)
    - National Congress of Neighborhood Women (Box 682, Folder 1)
    - Women's Action Alliance, Inc. (Box 682, Folder 2)
    - National Women's Health Network (Box 682, Folder 3)
  - Youth, 1977-1981; 35; 4.27 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Youth - A-Z, 1
      - Youth - A-C (Box 682, Folder 5)
      - Youth - C-M (Box 683, Folder 1-4)
      - Youth - N-Z (Box 684, Folder 1-3)
      - Boys Clubs of America (Box 684, Folder 4)
      - Boys Clubs of New York - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 684, Folder 5)
      - Boys Clubs of New York (Box 685, Folder 1)
      - Boys Clubs of St. Croix (Box 685, Folder 2)
      - Boys Scouts of America - A-Z (Box 685, Folder 3-4)
      - Children's Aid Society (Box 685, Folder 5)
      - Children's Cultural Foundation (Box 685, Folder 6)
      - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York (Box 686, Folder 1-2)
      - Covenant House (Box 686, Folder 3)
      - Girls Scout of America (Box 686, Folder 4)
      - Printed Material (Box 687, Folder 1)
      - Putnam's Children Center (Box 687, Folder 2)
      - Save the Children Federation (Box 687, Folder 3)
      - Voluntary National Service System (Box 687, Folder 4)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) (Box 687, Folder 5)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Greater New York (Box 687, Folder 6)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - Contributions (Box 687, Folder 7)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) (Box 688, Folder 1)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board (Box 688, Folder 2)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Contributions (Box 688, Folder 3)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Board of Trustees (Box 688, Folder 4)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Minutes-Meetings (Box 688, Folder 5)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Printed Matter (Box 688, Folder 6)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Finances (Box 689, Folder 1)
    - Camps, 2
      - Youth Camps (Box 689, Folder 2)
      - Fresh Air Fund (Box 689, Folder 3)
    - Youth Project, 3
      - Youth Project (Box 690, Folder 1)
      - Youth Project - A-C (Box 690, Folder 2-4)
      - Youth Project - D-Z (Box 691, Folder 1-2)
      - Campaign for Political Rights (Box 691, Folder 3)
      - Contributions (Box 691, Folder 4, Box 692, Folder 1)
    - Homes, 4
      - Youth Homes - A-Z (Box 692, Folder 2)
  - X-Y-Z, 1977-1981; 36; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - X-Y - Miscellaneous (Box 682, Folder 4)
    - Z - Miscellaneous (Box 692, Folder 3)
  - Audiovisual materials, 37; 0.24 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box
    Sound recordings; Moving Images
    - Arts - Publications - American National Heritage Association - The Sound of Quinto Lingo FRENCH, 1977 November; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15642)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - NYCOM Graduation - Dr. Schure and Dr. Riland, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11186)